Guide to the Samuel Rossiter Betts Autograph Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Autograph Collection, Series I
  - Saltonstall, Gurdon, 1725 (Box 4, Folder 373-374)
  - Sanford, Charles F., 1847 (Box 4, Folder 375)
  - Schuyler, Eugene, 1859 (Box 4, Folder 376)
  - Schwab, John C., 1886 (Box 4, Folder 377)
  - Scott, John M., 1746 (Box 4, Folder 378)
  - Seeley, John E., 1835 (Box 4, Folder 379)
  - Seymour, David L., 1826 (Box 4, Folder 380)
  - Seymour, Edward W., 1853 (Box 4, Folder 381)
  - Seymour, Horatio, 1797 (Box 4, Folder 382)
  - Seymour, O S, 1824 (Box 4, Folder 383)
  - Seymour, Thomas D., 1870 Honorary (Box 4, Folder 384)
  - Sherman, John (Box 4, Folder 385)
  - Sherman, Roger, 1768 Honorary (Box 4, Folder 386)
  - Sherman, Roger M., 1792 (Box 4, Folder 387)
  - Shiras, George, 1853 (Box 4, Folder 388)
  - Sill, Edward R., 1861 (Box 4, Folder 389)
  - Silliman, B D, 1824 (Box 4, Folder 390)
  - Sloane, Thomas C., 1868 (Box 4, Folder 391)
  - Smalley, George W., 1853 (Box 4, Folder 392)
  - Smith, E C, 1875 (Box 4, Folder 393)
  - Smith, John Cotton, 1783, 1830 (Box 4, Folder 394-395)
  - Smith, Nathan (Box 4, Folder 396)
  - Smith, Truman, 1815 (Box 4, Folder 397)
  - Smith, W. N.H., 1834 (Box 4, Folder 398)
  - Smith, William, 1719-1745 (Box 4, Folder 399-400)
  - Spalding, Rufus P., 1807 (Box 4, Folder 401)
  - Sprague, William B., 1815 (Box 4, Folder 402)
  - Spring, Gardiner, 1805 (Box 4, Folder 403)
  - Stebbins, Daniel, 1788 (Box 4, Folder 404)
  - Stedman, Edmund, 1853 (Box 4, Folder 405)
  - Sterling, Micah, 1804 (Box 4, Folder 406)
  - Stevens, Alex H., 1854 (Box 4, Folder 407)
  - Stevens, John A., 1813 (Box 4, Folder 408)
  - Stewart, William M., 1852 (Box 4, Folder 409)
  - Stiles, Abel, 1733 (Box 4, Folder 410)
  - Stiles, Ezra, 1746 (Box 4, Folder 411)
  - Stoeckel, Gustave J., 1864 Honorary (Box 4, Folder 412)
  - Stokes, Anson P., Jr., 1896 (Box 4, Folder 413)
  - Storrs, Henry R., 1804 (Box 4, Folder 414)
  - Storrs, William L., 1814 (Box 4, Folder 415)
  - Story, Joseph (Box 4, Folder 416)
  - Stowe, Harriet Beecher (Box 4, Folder 417)
  - Strong, Jedidiah, 1761 (Box 4, Folder 418)
  - Strong, Nehemiah, 1755 (Box 4, Folder 419)
  - Strong, Selah B., 1811 (Box 4, Folder 420)
  - Strong, William, 1828 (Box 4, Folder 421)
  - Stuart, Moses, 1799 (Box 4, Folder 422)
  - Sturges, Hezekiah, 1841 (Box 4, Folder 423)
  - Sturges, Jonathan, 1759 (Box 4, Folder 424)
  - Sumner, Charles (Box 5, Folder 425)
  - Sumner, William G., 1863 (Box 5, Folder 426)
  - Swan, Thomas W., 1900 (Box 5, Folder 427)
  - Swayne, Noah, 1865 Honorary (Box 5, Folder 428)
  - Swayne, Wager, 1856 (Box 5, Folder 429)
  - Swift, Zephaniah, 1778 (Box 5, Folder 430)
  - Taft, Alphonso, 1833 (Box 5, Folder 431)
  - Taft, William Howard, 1878 (Box 5, Folder 432)
  - Tallmadge, Benjamin, 1773 (Box 5, Folder 433)
  - Tallmadge, Frederick A., 1811 (Box 5, Folder 434)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel, 1745 (Box 5, Folder 435)
  - Taylor, Nathaniel W., 1807 (Box 5, Folder 436)
  - Taylor, Richard, 1845 (Box 5, Folder 437)
  - Ten Eyck, Henry J., 1879 (Box 5, Folder 438)
  - Thacher, Thomas, 1871 (Box 5, Folder 439)
  - Thacher, Thomas A., 1835 (Box 5, Folder 440)
  - Thomas, Elisha S., 1858 (Box 5, Folder 441)
  - Thompson, Joseph P., 1838 (Box 5, Folder 442)
  - Thompson, Smith, 1824 Honorary (Box 5, Folder 443)
  - Tilden, Samuel J., 1837 (Box 5, Folder 444)
  - Tomlinson, Gideon, 1802 (Box 5, Folder 445)
  - Tracy, Charles, 1832 (Box 5, Folder 446)
  - Tracy, Uriah, 1778 (Box 5, Folder 447)
  - Treadwell, John, 1767 (Box 5, Folder 448)
  - Trumbull, Benjamin, 1759 (Box 5, Folder 449)
  - Trumbull, J H, 1842 (Box 5, Folder 450)
  - Trumbull, Jonathan, 1779 Honorary, 1797 Honorary (Box 5, Folder 451-452)
  - Trumbull, John, 1767 (Box 5, Folder 453-454)
  - Twichell, Joseph H., 1859 (Box 5, Folder 455)
  - Twining, Alexander C., 1820 (Box 5, Folder 456)
  - Tyler, Morris F., 1870 (Box 5, Folder 457)
  - Tyler, Moses C., 1857 (Box 5, Folder 458)
  - Van Buren, James H., 1873 (Box 5, Folder 459)
  - Van Buren, John, 1828 (Box 5, Folder 460)
  - Vanderbilt, Cornelius, 1894 Honorary (Box 5, Folder 461)
  - Van Name, Addison, 1858 (Box 5, Folder 462)
  - Van Rensselaer, Jacob R., 1786 (Box 5, Folder 463)
  - Varnum, James M., 1868 (Box 5, Folder 464)
  - Varnum, Joseph B, 1838 (Box 5, Folder 465)
  - Vincent, Boyd, 1867 (Box 5, Folder 466)
  - Vincent, George E., 1885 (Box 5, Folder 467)
  - Wadsworth, James, 1748, 1787 (Box 5, Folder 468-469)
  - Wadsworth, James S., ex-1829 Law (Box 5, Folder 470)
  - Wadsworth, James W., Jr., 1898 (Box 5, Folder 471)
  - Waite, Morrison R., 1837 (Box 5, Folder 472)
  - Waldo, Daniel, 1788 (Box 5, Folder 473)
  - Washburn, William B., 1844 (Box 5, Folder 474)
  - Washington, Booker T. (Box 5, Folder 475)
  - Wayland, Francis, 1881 Honorary (Box 5, Folder 476)
  - Webb, Nathaniel, 1757 (Box 5, Folder 477)
  - Webster, Daniel (Box 5, Folder 478)
  - Webster, Noah, 1778 (Box 5, Folder 479)
  - Weed, Thurlow (Box 5, Folder 480)
  - West, Stephen, 1755 (Box 5, Folder 481)
  - Wetmore, George P., 1867 (Box 5, Folder 482)
  - Wharton, Francis, 1839 (Box 5, Folder 483)
  - White, Andrew D., 1853 (Box 5, Folder 484)
  - Whiting, Nathan, 1743 (Box 5, Folder 485)
  - Whitney, Eli, 1792 (Box 5, Folder 486)
  - Whitney, Josiah D., 1839 (Box 5, Folder 487)
  - Whitney, William C., 1863 (Box 5, Folder 488)
  - Whitney, William D., 1867 Honorary (Box 5, Folder 489)
  - Whittier, John G. (Box 5, Folder 490)
  - Williams, Elisha (Box 5, Folder 491)
  - Williams, Thomas S., 1794 (Box 5, Folder 492)
  - Williams, Thomas W., 1838 (Box 5, Folder 493)
  - Willis, Nathaniel P., 1827 (Box 5, Folder 494)
  - Willis, Richard S., 1841 (Box 5, Folder 495)
  - Winthrop, Buchanan, 1862 (Box 5, Folder 496)
  - Wolcott, Oliver, 1747, 1778 (Box 5, Folder 497-498)
  - Woodford, Stewart L., 1854 (Box 5, Folder 499)
  - Woods, William B., 1845 (Box 5, Folder 500)
  - Woodworth, John, 1788 (Box 5, Folder 501)
  - Woolsey, Theodore D., 1820 (Box 5, Folder 502)
  - Wooster, David, 1738 (Box 5, Folder 503)
  - Worchester, Joseph E., 1811 (Box 5, Folder 504)
  - Worthington, John, 1740 (Box 5, Folder 505)
  - Wright, Elizur, 1826 (Box 5, Folder 506)
  - Wyllys, George, 1729 (Box 5, Folder 507)
  - Yale, Elihu (Box 5, Folder 508)
  - Yale University (Box 5, Folder 509)
  - Young, Mason, 1860 (Box 5, Folder 510)
- Samuel R. Betts Papers, Series II
  - Correspondence re: dinner for Cambridge and Yale track teams, 1895 September (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - "Yale College Prize Essays and Orations by Samuel R. Betts", 1873-1875 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Lists of Samuel R. Betts's book donations, inventory of personal effects, miscellaneous, 1909-1928, undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Additional Autographs, Series III
  - Anthon, William (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Betts, Samuel R. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Buchanan, James (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Catron, J. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Cutting, Francis B. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Farragut, David G. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Forsythe, John (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Francis, John W. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Logan, John A. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Longfellow, Henry Wadsworth (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Sheridan, Philip H. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Story, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Wright, Silas (Box 6, Folder 4)